Synced and corrected by martythecrazy
www.addic7ed.com
Kor sub: bravesfan
[Insects buzzing]
실망스럽군
Disappointing.
[Keypad beeping]
[Ringing]
다음은 누구야?
Who's next?
も
Bangarang! (Bass!)
bangarang
take me under
라큅씨, 브라운 형사입니다
Mr. Raqib. Detective Brown.
협박에 대한 최근의 정보때문에
In light of recent threats,
당신네 정부가 라스베가스 경찰에게
your government has asked
the Las Vegas police
to ensure your safety during your stay.
당신의 체류기간동안 안전하게
보호해 줄 것을 요청했습니다
우리가 모든 상황을 통제중입니다
We have the situation under control.
걸어가면서 형사님에게
No harm in walking the detective
보안태세를 알려드리게, 파리드
through your preparations, Farid.
[Elevator bell dings]
감시카메라가 있고
Cameras.
128 비트로 암호화된 출입문입니다
128-bit encryption on the door.
완벽한 보안이 되어 있습니다
We are completely secure.
- [Air hisses]
- bangarang
잘있었나, 칼
Hey, Cal.
빌어먹을, 케인
Damn it, Kane.
알렉스네요
잘있었어요, 알렉스
It's Alex. Hi, Alex.
좋은 아침이에요, 샤다
_
케인씨, 여기서 뭐하는겁니까?
Mr. Kane, what are you doing here?
확실히, 당신네 정부도 보안상태를
Brown: Apparently, your
government also decided to hire
점검하기 위해서 라스베가스에서
제일 잘나가는 꼴통 보안 컨설턴트를
Vegas' biggest pain-in-the-ass
security consultant
고용하기로 결정했군요
to test your preparations.
축하합니다. 당신은 실패했어요
Congratulations. You failed.
발코니를 봉쇄했나요?
They're sealing off the balcony?
침입하기 쉬운 지점이죠
It's an easy point of entry.
22층 높이를요? 말도 안돼요
22 floors up? That's ridiculous.
라큅씨는 미국 대통령보다 더 나은
Farid: Mr. Raqib has better protection
보호를 받고 있습니다
than the president of the United States.
그거 잘됐군요, 6명의 대통령이
암살당한 사실을 제외하면요
Well, that would be a comfort,
except they shot six presidents.
부엌에 또한 봉쇄되지 않은
There's also an unsecured
음식조달 통로가 있습니다
catering entrance in the kitchen.
거기도 봉쇄하세요
Lock that down, too.
싫습니다. 유감스럽게도 나는
명령을 받지 않을꺼요
No, with all due respect,
I will not be lectured.
삐친게 느껴져?
Feel all that respect?
오, 그럼. 내가 처리할께
Oh, yeah. I'll handle it.
- [Door opens]
- [Chuckles]
어떻게 그렇게 일을 하는거죠?
How do you do that?
나쁜놈들이 무엇을 할지
어떻게 파악하는거죠?
How do you figure out what
bad guys are gonna do?
나쁜놈처럼 생각하는거죠
Think like a bad guy.
악당이 되지 않고 어떻게
나쁜놈처럼 생각하는거죠?
How do you think like a bad
guy without being a bad guy?
위협이 얼마나 심각한거야?
How bad were the threats?
그가 하고 있는 무역 협상이
The trade deal he's negotiating
저 사람의 고국의 보수파들을
열받게 하고 있지만
ticked off the old guard
back in his country,
10억 달러 가치가 있기 때문에...
but it's worth $1 billion, so...
실례합니다
Excuse me.
왜그래?
What?
저 자는 여기서 일하는 사람이 아니야
상의는 맞는데 바지가 틀려
That guy doesn't work here.
Right jacket. Wrong pants.
젠장
Shoot.
그자가 엘리베이터 키카드와
통신기를 가져갔어
He's got the elevator key card
and the communication set.
파리드에게 연락할께
I'll call Farid.
서비스 엘리베이터를 타고 옥상으로 갈께
I'm gonna take the service
elevator to the roof.
괜찮을꺼야
It's all right.
[Guns cock]
も
[Elevator bell dings]
침입 지점이라고 말씀드렸잖아요
It's a point of entry.
무쉬니 그랑 크루
1924년 산이에요
Musigny Grand Cru 1924.
꼭 그걸로 때려눕혔어야 했습니까?
Did you have to hit him with that?
정치적인 이유인것 같아
- [Siren wailing]
- It looks political.
라큅을 그의 조국 국민들을
배신한 죄로 몰고
Accused Raqib of crimes against his people,
기타 등등...이것저것
et cetera, et cetera.
가족들은 뭐 얘기한것 없어?
Family say anything to you?
다우드는 내가 자기 와인을
쏟았다고 뭐라하던데
Daoud's bitching I spilled his wine.
- 부자들이란...
- 그래...부자들이란
- Rich people.
- Yeah, rich people.
이봐, 가자구
맥주 한잔 살께
- [Cellphone chimes, vibrates]
- Hey, come on. You earned a beer.
나중에 하지. 지니 전화야
만나러 가야해
Rain check. It's Ginny.
I got to go meet her.
물론이지, 자네 부인한테 인사 전해주게
Of course. Say hi to the wife for me.
전부인이야
Ex-wife.
전부인하고 저녁을 같이 먹고
The ex-wife you have dinner with,
집 수리도 하고 말이야
fix stuff around the house.
이혼 서류에 싸인 하긴 했어?
You even sign the divorce papers yet?
이혼 서류에 대해 자네가
마지막으로 얘기했을때...
Last time you even mentioned
the divorce papers was...
- 복잡한 일이라 그래
- 오...
- It's complicated.
- Oh.
자네가 제정신이라면,
지니하고 잘 해결을 보려고 노력해야지
You had any sense, you'd
make it work with Ginny.
내가 제정신이면,
옥상에서 뛰어내리지 않겠지
If I had any sense, I wouldn't
be jumping off of buildings.
[Siren wailing]
- 오늘 수고했어
- 그래
- Good job today.
- Yep.
Well, I don't want
to let this moment go
[Slot machine dinging, coins clinking]
No, I don't want to let
this moment go, oh, oh
try to slow down time
닥터 리
Hmm. Dr. Lee.
케인씨
Mr. Kane.
살아 돌아온걸 축하하며
To coming back alive.
당신이 피했던 일을 마친고 온것을 위하여
Any landing you walk away from.
Mmm!
공항에서 바로 온거야?
Did you come straight from the airport?
튀니지 해안에서 3개월간 트롤선을 타고
Three months on a trawler
off the coast of Tunisia
바다에서 피난민들을 구조했어
pulling refugees out of the water.
두가지 일을 하고 싶었지...
I got two things on my to-do list...
술 한잔 하는것과
뜨거운 물로 샤워하는거
To get a drink and a hot
shower, in that order.
Well, I don't want
to let this moment go
나는 병원드로 돌아가서
So, I'm, uh, hopping
수술 팀에 복귀하려고 해
back on my surgical
rotation at the hospital.
한동안 집에 머무를꺼야
I'm gonna be home a while.
가까이 있는다니 기쁘네
Well, it'll be nice to have you around.
아주 쬐금...보고 싶었어
I missed you a little bit.
알아. 내가 매력적이잖아
I know. I'm awesome.
[Chuckles]
[Glasses clink]
Ohh!
집에 데려다줄꺼야?
Drive me home?
차로 태워다 주기만 해
Just a ride.
술은 마셨고, 이제 샤워를 하고 싶거든
I had my drink, and now I want my shower.
좋아
Fine.
하지만 집에 들어가지는 않을꺼야
But I am not coming in.
When push comes to shove
I choose what I love
Ohh!
그냥 친구로 하는거지?
Just doing the friend thing, right?
그래
Yeah.
나한테도 친구처럼 느껴지네
This feels friendly to me.
음..맛있어. 진짜 그리웠다구
Mmm. God, I have missed these.
Mmm!
당신도 그리웠어
Well, you, too.
하지만 시리얼이 진짜 그리웠지
- [Chuckles]
- But mostly the cereal.
Wow.
여기서 다시 우리가 함께
살려고 하는건 아니지?
We're not exactly moving on
with our lives here, are we?
우리는 그냥 친구야
We're just friends.
때때로는 아주 친한 친구지
Very friendly friends sometimes.
아직도 결혼 반지를 끼고 있는
전부인이라는 말이군
Says the ex-wife who still
wears her wedding ring.
반지를 계속 끼는건 오직...
그래야 다른 의사들이 나한테 치근덕대지 않거든
I only wear this because, uh...
So the doctors don't hit on me.
Oh.
그리고 아무도 당신의
부끄러운걸 못보니까 말이지
And so nobody can see your shame.
그냥 문신일 뿐이야!
It's just a tattoo!
난 19살이었고, 당신은 이게
귀엽다고 말하곤 했잖아
I was 19, and you used
to tell me it was cute.
그래, 내가 거짓말 했었던거지
Yeah, I was lying.
왜 우리는 계속 원점으로 돌아올까?
Why do we keep coming back?
You can trust me
오늘 경호를 했던...
라큅 가족 말이야...
This family today... The Raqibs...
몇번 그들의 경호를 맡았었어
I've worked with them a couple of times.
그집 딸은 정말 똑똑해
Their daughter's real smart.
나에게 묻기를,
"어떻게 악당이 되지 않고
She asked me, "how do
you think like a bad guy
나쁜놈 처럼 생각할 수 있죠?"
라고 하더군
without being a bad guy?"
우리가 만났을때가 생각이 났어
Reminds me of when we met.
Hmm.
내가 당신의 상처를
봉합하기 전이야 후야?
Was that before or after I sewed you up?
[Chuckles]
내말은 "그래, 내가 악당인적이 있어서
It's just there was a
time I would have said,
나쁜놈 처럼 생각할 수 있지"라고
말할수 있는 때가 있었다는거야
"yeah, it makes me a
bad guy because I was."
그랬었지
You were.
더 이상 그런 사람이 아니야
You are not that man anymore.
왜 사람들은 복잡하게 생각하는거야?
Why do people make it so complicated?
우리가 하는 일이 현재의 우리야
We are what we do.
좋은 일을 하면,
당신은 좋은 사람인거야
Do good, you are good.
당신이 나를 구해낸거야, 지니
You pulled me out of that life, Ginny.
아니 정말이야. 당신이 한거야
No. Yeah, you did. Hey.
당신이 어떻게 해야하는지를 보여준거야
You showed me how.
우리 사이에 무슨일이 생겨도 나는...
No matter what happens between us, I'm...
나는 늘 그점에 감사할꺼야
I'm always gonna be grateful for that.
[Groans]
왜 우리는 결혼생활에 엉망인거지?
Why do we suck so much at being married?
오, 우린 정말로, 정말로
부부로써는 엉망이야
Oh, we're really, really bad at it.
[Sighs]
그러니까, 왜 결혼했던거지?
So, why be married?
내말은, 왜 우리가 그런 규정에
얽매여서 살아야 하는거지?
I mean, why do we have
to play by those rules?
무슨 말이야?
What are you saying?
내 말은...
I'm saying...
집에 있으라고
Stay.
[Chuckles]
당신을 사랑해, 그리고...
I love you, and...
나머지는, 닥치는대로 우리가
헤쳐나갈수 있을꺼야
The rest, we could just
figure it out as it comes.
나도 사랑해
I love you, too.
[Chuckles]
You can trust me
oh, oh, oh, oh-oh
trust me
trust, trust me
[Dog barking in distance]
[Gun cocks]
알렉스!
Ginny: Alex!
[Screams]
지니!
- Ginny!
- [Gunshot]
안돼, 안돼, 지니
No, no, Ginny.
안돼
No.
안돼, 리지, 안돼
No, Ginny. No.
も
[Indistinct chatter]
[Horns blaring]
이봐!
Man: Hey!
[Tires screech]
[Gun clicking]
[Tires squeal]
출발해! 출발해!
Man: Go! Go!
[Tires squeal]
[Footsteps approaching]
유감이에요, 알렉스
[British accent] Sorry about that, Alex.
[Footsteps fade]
[Tires squeal]
[Engine revs]
[Gunshot]
[Knock on door]
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
이봐, 친구, 정말 유감이야
Hey, buddy. I'm real sorry.
자네한테 질문을 좀 해야해
I need to ask you some questions.
그래
Yeah.
케인씨,
Mr. Kane,
어젯밤 닥터 버지니아 리씨가 집에서
살해된채 발견됐을때
when Dr. Virginia Lee was found
murdered in her home last night,
당신은 누군가 있었다고 주장했습니다
you claimed someone else was present.
벌거벗은채로 추적을 했습니다
We ran down the strip.
수백명은 핸드폰으로
그 자를 찍었을겁니다
A hundred people got
the guy on their phones.
그게, 수많은 사람들은 당신이
Well, lots of people filmed you
속옷만 입고 나체로 뛰는걸 찍었습니다
running down the middle of
the strip in your underwear.
아무도 당신이 쫓던 사람을
확인해주지 못했습니다
No one confirms the other
man when you were fleeing...
나를 차로 친 여자...
그녀는 그를 봤습니다
The woman who hit me with
the car... she saw him.
그녀를 찾을 수 없습니다
We can't locate her.
당신이 말한 번호판은
일치하는 번호가 없습니다
The plates you gave don't
match any existing plates.
[Recorder beeps]
- 우리는 친구잖아
- 우린 친구지
- We're friends.
- We are.
그리고 곧, 니가 내 친구라서
나를 이 사건에서
And real soon, they're
gonna pull me off this case
제외를 시킬꺼고
because you're my friend
진실을 밝히는것보다 사건 해결 건수에
and put on some guy who cares
더 관심이 많은 누군가를 배정하겠지
more about his clearance
rate than the truth.
넌 살해도구를 손에 쥔채로 발견됐다고
You were found with the damn
murder weapon in your hand.
정신차려, 자네는 FBI였었잖아
Come on. You were FBI.
여성이 살해됐을때 첫번째 규칙이 뭐야
What's the number-one rule
when a woman gets killed?
늘 남편이 살인범이다
Together: The husband always did it.
알렉스, 뭔가를 나에게 알려줘
왜냐하면 지금 이 순간에도
Alex, give me something, because right now,
지니의 살인범을 찾으러 나가야 하는
모든 경찰들이 자네에 대한
every cop we want out there
looking for Ginny's killer
증거를 찾고 있다고
is out making a case against you.
칼, 우린 함께 하기로 했었어
Cal, we were getting back together.
어젯밤, 우리는 결정을 했었다고
Last night, we decided.
지니를 살해한 자를 내가 봤어
I saw the guy who murdered Ginny.
내가 그놈을 찾아서, 내가 끝내버릴꺼야
I'm gonna find him, and I'm gonna end him.
- 나한테...나한테 손대지마
- 이봐, 기다려, 알렉스!
- Don't touch... don't touch me.
- Hey, wait. Hey. Alex!
- 길을 비켜
- 알렉스!
- Out of my way.
- Alex!
당신은 어디도 갈수 없습니다, 케인씨!
You're going nowhere, Mr. Kane!
바닥에 엎드려!
Get down on the ground!
자네가 도망가면
내가 도와줄수 없다구, 알렉스
I can't help you if you run, Alex.
이봐, 이봐, 진정하라구, 친구
- [Grunting]
- Hey, hey, hey. Come on, man.
이건 자네의 본모습이 아니야
This isn't you.
아니 맞아, 이게 나야!
No, it is. This is me!
[Police radio chatter]
그를 잘 감시하게
Watch him.
알겠습니다
Yes, sir.
[Door closes]
も
[Car alarm blaring]
이봐! 뭐하는거야?!
Hey! What are you doing?!
[Police siren chirps]
제대로 시간을 맞췄네
- About damn time.
- [Siren wailing]
[Tires squealing]
당신 도대체 누구야?
Who the hell are you?
나는 카산드라에요
I'm Cassandra.
당신은 알렉산더 케인이고요
You are Alexander Kane.
콴티코에서 최고 성적을 받았었죠
Top in your class at Quantico.
시스템 분석 전문가이구요
Specialized in systems analysis.
FBI는 당신을 합동 안보 작전에
파견을 보냈었지요
Feds loaned you out to
joint security operations.
당신은 유럽 아시아 전체 지역에서
2년간 테러리스트들을
You spent two years hunting terrorists
소탕하는데 보냈어요
all over Europe and Asia.
그래, 내 이력서에서 알아낸거겠지
Yeah, you could have pulled
that off my r챕sum챕.
미 정부의 명령을 따르지 않고
Against direct orders from
the United States government,
이브라힘 체칙을 정면에서 쏴버렸죠
you shot Ibrahim Chechik in the face.
당신이 망가졌을때도,
When you broke bad,
당신은 허송세월하지 않았어요
you didn't screw around, boy scout.
- 당신 MI6야?
- 더 큰 곳이죠
- Are you MI6?
- Bigger.
- NSA야?
- 더 커요
- NSA?
- Bigger.
그런 곳은 없어
There's no such thing.
[Tires screech]
[Wailing continues]
좋아요, 저들이 내 번호판을 조회했겠군요
Okay, they just called in my plates.
멋진 일이 생길꺼에요
So here's something cool.
[Wailing stops]
[Helicopter blades whirring]
불가능해
That's impossible.
"불가능"하다구요, 좋아요
그렇게 생각하세요
"Impossible." Good. Stay with that.
불가능이란것에 대하여
생각을 좀 바꿔보세요, 알렉스
I need you to wrap your head
around impossible, Alex.
만약 당신이 불가능이라는것에 대하여
믿지 않는 다면 사람들이 죽게될거에요
People will die if you do
not belive in the impossible
앞으로...8분 6초 후부터요
in the next... Eight
minutes and six seconds.
[Tires screech]
[Console dinging]
이건 아주 비정상적이야
Well, this is highly irregular.
하지만 규칙에는 벗어나지 않았죠
But within the rules.
케인씨, 내 이름은 미스터 존슨입니다
Mr. Kane, my name is Mr. Johnson.
당신에게 이야기 해줄 것들을
The next thing I'm about to say to you
당신은 믿지 않을것입니다
you're not going to believe.
대부분의 사람들이 믿지 않죠
Most people don't.
그럴수도 있다고 생각합니다
I won't take it personally.
꽤 오래전에
Johnson: A considerable time ago,
매우 부유한 사람들의 집단에서
a group of extremely wealthy individuals
범죄를 예측하는 시스템을 개발했지요
developed a system to predict crime.
그게 다에요?
그게 당신의 이야기입니까?
That's it? That's your story?
당신들 미쳤군요
범죄를 예측하는건...
You're crazy. Predicting crime is...
불가능하다구요?
알렉스, 제발요
Impossible? Yes, Alex. Come on.
6분 55초 남았어요
당신에게 주어진 시간은요
6 minutes and 55 seconds.
You need to catch up.
범죄를 예측할 수는 없어요
너무 많은 변수들이 있다구요
You can't predict crime.
There's too many variables.
그렇게 생각할수도 있죠
One would think.
하지만 한가지 상수가 있지요...
인간의 본성이요...
But there is one
constant... Human nature...
우리가 바라는 것을 취하기 위해
죄를 저지를 수 있는 의지요
Our willingness to commit
sin to get what we desire.
인간의 본성을 이해한다면
You understand human nature,
나머지는 그냥 데이터 분석이에요
and then the rest is just data analysis.
우리는 무기 구매와 라스베가스로 향하는
범죄자들을 추적했어요
We tracked weapon purchases,
criminals on flights to Vegas.
라큅의 개인 이메일이 해킹됐어요
Raqib's personal e-mail hacked.
납치의 조건에 부합해요
Profile fits a kidnapping.
그리고 데이터 분석 파트요
And the data-analysis part.
딸을 납치할때, 그의 부인을 죽여
Man: When you take the
girl, kill the mother.
부인을 죽이면,
라큅은 딸을 구하기 위해
Kill the mother, and Raqib will do
- 우리가 요구하는 무엇이든 할꺼야
- 샤다를 납치하고, 라큅 부인을 죽인다고?
- whatever we ask to save the girl.
- Kidnap Shada, kill Mrs. Raqib?
우리 계산에 따르면
5대 1의 확률로 납치를 하는동안
We calculate five-to-one during the snatch,
그들은 사고로 샤다를 죽일수 있고,
they accidentally kill Shada,
3대2의 확률로,
몇몇 선량한 사람들이
and three-to-two, some innocent bystanders
총격전에 사망할거에요
are murdered in the crossfire.
어제 그자. 그자는 납치범이 아니었어
That guy yesterday. He wasn't a kidnapper.
아니에요, 그는 라큅의 보안을 뚫는데
장애가 되는것을 시험해보기 위한 미끼였어요
No, he was a decoy sent to test
Raqib's security for obstacles.
그리고 그들은 하나를 찾았죠...
바로 당신이에요
And they found one... you.
그래서 그들은 당신을
죽이기 위해 사람을 보냈죠
And then they sent a man to kill you.
지니가 죽은건...
Ginny's dead because...
당신이 그녀와 함께 있어서였죠
Because you were with her.
우리 그룹은 당신이
이 납치를 막아주길 바랍니다
Our group would like you
to stop this kidnapping.
당신의 아내를 죽인 사람은
마음대로 하세요
Do what you wish with the
man who killed your wife.
이게 사실일리 없어
This can't be true.
간단하게 확인할 방법이 있죠...
아무것도 안하는겁니다
Well, there's a simple way
to find out... do nothing.
내 말은, 만약 당신 생각에 우리가
미쳤거나 거짓말한다고 생각한다면,
I mean, if you think we're insane or lying,
당신은 그곳에 그냥 서 있으세요 앞으로...
you can stand there for the next...
- 5분 13초 동안에요
- 그리고 아무일도 일어나지 않겠죠
- 5 minutes and 13 seconds.
- And nothing will happen.
하지만 만약 당신이 틀렸고
우리가 범죄를 예측할 수 있다면
But if you are wrong and
we can predict crime,
라큅 부인은 죽을것이고
that mother will die,
그녀의 딸은 지니를 살해한 사람에 의해
and her daughter will be abducted
납치가 될거에요
by the man who murdered Ginny.
케인씨, 내가 미친 사람처럼 보이나요?
Mr. Kane, do I look like I'm insane?
[Car door closes, engine turns over]
[Tires squeal]
게임이 시작됐습니다
The game has begun.
신사 숙녀 여러분, 베팅을 하세요
Ladies and gentlemen, place your bets.
[Engine revs]
[Horn blares]
911에 전화
- Dial 911.
- [Ringing]
911입니다. 어떤 긴급 상황이신가요?
Dispatcher: 911. What is your emergency?
- 납치를 신고하려고...
- 뭐요, 납치요?
- I need to report a kidnapp...
- What, a kidnapping?
[Grunts]
이게 처음이자 마지막
경고입니다, 케인씨
This is your first and
last warning, Mr. Kane.
당신은 우리 조직에 대한 것을
누구에게도 발설할 수 없습니다
You can tell no one the
truth about our organization.
당신은 범죄를 막기위해
당신이 가진 자산만을 사용해야 합니다
You need to use your own
resources to stop this crime.
[Horn honks]
그가 살아남을지 보자구
We'll see if he lives.
[Car door closes, engine turns over]
[Tires squealing]
[Horn honks]
전화 받아요
당신이 잊고 묻지 않은게 있어요
Take the phone. You forgot
to ask me a question.
당신도 내 자산에 포함됩니까?
Do you count as my resource?
그렇죠
There you go.
아무거나 물어보세요...
이성적인 한도내에서요
Ask me anything... Within reason.
제가 지원해드리죠
I shall provide.
증명해봐요
Prove it.
나는 4등급의 화재 대비 조정 장치의
I need the access code for a four-star
접속 코드가 필요해요
fire-system control panel.
모델 FJNN4R2에요
Model Foxtrot, Juliet,
Niner, Niner, 4 - Romeo - 2.
코드는 1003702에요
That's 1003702.
[Alarm blaring]
화재경보입니다
Fire alarm.
카지노에서 대피하십시오
Please clear the casino floor.
화재경보를 울리는게 어떻게
납치범을 찾는데 도움이 되는거죠?
And how does triggering the fire
alarm help find the kidnappers?
비상구를 찾지 않는 유일은 사람들일테니까
They're the only ones
not looking for an exit.
엎드려요! 엎드려!
Get down! Get down!
[Gunshots, people screaming]
- 나가, 나가, 나가!
- 엄마!
Move, move, move! Mom!
메디나를 여기서 대피시켜!
Get Medina out of here!
알렉스!
Alex!
가자! 가자!
Man: Go! Go!
も
저쪽이요
That way.
[Gunshots]
Ohh! Ohh!
알렉스!
Shada: Alex!
라스베가스 경잘이다!
무기를 버려!
Officer: LVPD! Drop your weapons!
저쪽이다!
Over there!
も
- 뭐 발견했나?
- 아무것도 없습니다
- Anything?
- Officer: Got nothing.
알렉스 케인에 대해 지명수배를 내려
Put out an APB on Alex Kane.
무장했고 위험한 자다
He is armed and dangerous.
も
좋은 일을 하면, 당신은 좋은 사람이야
Ginny: Do good. You are good.
[Door opens, closes]
[Computer beeping]
_
[Indistinct conversations]
[Elevator bell dings]
당신이 그를 이곳으로 오게 했군
You led him here.
Huh.
용인해줄수 없어
Unacceptable.
그에게 단서를 남겼을 뿐이에요
I left him a clue. That's all.
이해할 수 있는 기회를요
A chance to understand.
그가 얻어낸거죠
He earned it.
케인씨, 놀랍군요
Mr. Kane. What a surprise.
어서요
Please.
들어오세요
Come in.
케인씨, 이곳이
This is the house, Mr. Kane,
범죄 활동의 확률이
where the probabilities
of criminal activity
결정되는 하우스입니다
(하우스는 도박장을 부르는 말)
are determined.
하우스에는 언제난 두명이 상주하죠
There are always two members of the house.
카산드라는 딜러이고
저는 핏 보스(테이블 책임자)입니다
Cassandra is the dealer,
and I am the pit boss.
당신은 범죄를 예측할 수 있다고
했어요. 어떻게 하는거죠?
You said you can predict crime. How?
전보를 치던 시절 이후부터
우리는 세계의 정보 인프라
We've been inside the world's
information infrastructure
내부에 존재해 있었습니다
since the days of telegraph wire.
전화가 발명되면,
우리는 감청을 했지요
When phones arrived, we tapped them.
보안 카메라가 탄생했을때
When security cameras were born,
우리가 안면인식 소프트웨어를 설치했지요
we installed facial-recognition software.
경찰 기관의 메인프레임에
백도어를 설치했고,
Backdoors into law-enforcement mainframes,
금융 및 이메일 서버에
스파이웨어를 심었어요
spyware in financial and e-mail servers.
에이더, 알렉스 케인의 파일을 띄워
Ada, bring up our files on Alex Kane.
보시는 바와 같이
As you can see,
우리는 꽤 오랜동안 당신을 주시했어요
we've been following
you for a little while.
세상은 이미 스스로를
감시하고 있습니다, 케인씨
The world is already
watching itself, Mr. Kane.
우리는 단지 주목을 하는 것이죠
We just happen to be paying attention.
범죄를 예측하는 시스템을 개발한 사람들은
You see, the men who developed
a system to predict crime
이타심으로 그렇게 한 것이 아닙니다
didn't do so out of a sense of altruism.
그들은 도박사들이죠
They're gamblers.
거부들은 도박을 아주 좋아하죠
우리같은 평범한 사람들 보다 아주 많이요
The very rich love to gamble,
even more than the rest of us.
만약 당신이 아주 많은 돈이 있다면
But when you have so much money
변화를 느낄만큼 충분히
돈을 잃을수가 없어요
you could never lose enough
to make a difference,
평범한 도박은 진부해지죠
ordinary games become stale.
그래서 다른 도박들을
찾기 시작하게 됩니다
So you begin to look for other games...
아주 높은 위험율을 가진 도박들을요
Games with higher stakes.
범죄입니다, 케인씨
Crime, Mr. Kane.
우리는 범죄에 돈을 겁니다
We gamble on crime.
당신들은 사람들의 목숨에 도박을 하는거요
You gamble with people's lives.
아니요, 여기 하우스 안에서는
우리는 범죄를 예측합니다
No, here in the house, we predict crime.
범죄에 영향을 주지 않습니다
We never influence it.
당신들은 납치를 예측했었소?
Did you predict the kidnapping?
지니의 죽음을 예측했어요?
Did you predict Ginny's death?
당신들은 지니를 살릴수도 있었어
You could have saved Ginny.
케인씨...
Do not...
포기하지 말아요
(fold: 포커에서 죽는다는 말)
fold, Mr. Kane.
당신은 그럴만한 충분한 능력이 없어요
You don't have a strong enough hand.
[Exhales sharply]
왜 나에게 이걸 보여주는겁니까?
Why show me this?
왜 나에게 이야기해준거죠?
Why tell me this?
양쪽이 존재하지 않으면
베팅에 의미가 있을까요?
What's the point of a bet
unless you have two sides?
토마스 에드리발리,
Tomas Edribali,
이스탄불 출신의 전문 납치범이에요
professional kidnapper out of Istanbul.
그가 라큅 가족을 목표로 했을때
그의 계획이 게임에 입력이 되었죠
When he targeted the Raqibs,
his plan entered the game.
그가 한쪽 플레이어에요
He was one side.
그리고 당신이 반대쪽 플레이어구요
And you were the other.
당신도 모르게 스스로 내기를 걸만한
플레이어가 된거에요
You unwittingly made this
a wager worth playing.
도박사들은 당신이 이 베팅을
마무리짓길 원합니다
The gamblers would like
you to finish this bet.
오늘 일찍 이것을 감청했어요
We intercepted this earlier.
아빠, 엄마, 제발
그들이 원하는걸 지불해주세요
Father, Mother, please
pay them what they want.
두분 모두 사랑해요
[Crying] I love you both.
두분 모두 정말 사랑해요
I love you both so much.
[ Sobs]
샤다와 지니는 사람들이야,
내기의 대상이 아니고
Shada and Ginny are people, not bets.
당신 파일을 봤어요, 알렉스
지니가 어떻게 당신을 구해준지 알아요
I've seen your file, Alex.
I know how Ginny saved you.
당신이 그때의 모습으로 돌아간다면
그녀는 존재한적이 없는게 되는거에요
You go back to being that man,
it's like she never existed.
우리와 함께라면...당신은 샤다를
구할 수 있는 확률이 높아집니다
Johnson: Well, you have a better
chance of saving Shada... With us.
당신은 바로 지금 여기에서
변화를 만들 수 있어요
You can make a difference
right here, right now.
아니면...
Or...
그냥 물러설 수도 있지요
You can walk away.
시간이 촉박해요, 알렉스
Time's running out, Alex.
당신들을 위해서 하는게 아니에요
I'm not doing this for you.
샤다와 지니를 위해서 하는겁니다
I'm doing it for Shada and Ginny.
일이 끝나면, 이곳으로 돌아와서
When I'm done, I'm gonna come back here
당신들을 저 창문 밖으로 던져버릴거에요
and throw you through that window.
브라보
[Chuckling] Bravo.
받아들이죠
- [Elevator bell dings]
- I'll take that bet.
[Monitor beeping steadily]
[Beeping accelerates]
[Breathing heavily]
나에게 뭘 주사한거지?
What did you put in me?
내가 의사와 결혼한적이 있었거든
I used to be married to a doctor.
몇가지 잔기술을 배웠지
I picked up a few tricks.
하미드, 누군가 라큅을
제거하라고 너를 보냈지
Hamid, somebody sent you after Raqib.
누구였지?
Who was it?
우리를 막을 수 없어
Cannot stop us.
그래, 넌 미끼였을 뿐이야
그들은 널 이용했던거야
Yeah, you were a decoy. They used you.
[Chuckles]
잘들어
Focus.
출입구 말이야...네가 들어오
음식 반입 출입구
Door... you came in
through the catering door.
누가 그곳이 열려있다고 얘기해줬지?
Who told you it was open?
[Laughs]
그의 부하들 조차 그를 싫어한다구
Even his own people hate him.
[Laughs]
내가 말했잖아요, 알렉스 케인은
납치범들중 한명이 아니었어요
I am telling you, Alex Kane
was not one of the kidnappers!
그가 나를 구해줬다구요!
He saved me!
메디나, 당신이 헷갈린거야
Medina, you're confused.
파리드는 보안팀장이야
Farid is head of security.
글쎄요, 그렇게 생각 안하는데요
Yeah, I wouldn't really go by that.
꼼짝하지 마세요, 라큅씨
Stay where you are, Mr. Raqib...
최소한 파리드가 당신들 딸이
어디있는지 말할때까지는요
At least until Farid here tells
us where your daughter is.
- 어떻게 이곳으로 들어온거야?
- 부엌 음식 반입 출입구요. 여전히 열려있더군
How did you get in here? Kitchen
catering entrance. It's still open.
당신이 그놈들 중 한명이라구?
Tell me you weren't a part of this.
납치범의 이름은 토마스 에드리발리입니다
The kidnapper's name is Tomas Edribali.
에드리발리는 부하들과
지속적으로 연락을 유지하죠
Edribali stayed in constant
touch with his crew.
만약 그에게 내부의 공범이 있다면,
If he has an inside man,
내부의 공범은 일회용 선불폰을
가지고 있을겁니다
that inside man has a burner phone on him.
저자야말로 당신들에게 총구를 겨누며
위협하는 사람입니다
He's the one pointing the gun at you.
그가...
He's the one...
Ohh!
우리에게 폰을 보여봐, 그렇지않으면
내가 널 조각조각 썰어버릴테니까
Show us this phone, or I will
cut it from you piece by piece!
Aah! Aah.
안주머니에...안주머니에
In the pocket. In the pocket.
Ohh.
전화를 걸어
You have a call to make.
[Ringing]
[Cellphone ringing, vibrating]
[Cellphone beeps]
왜 전화한거야?
Why are you calling?
모든것이 잘 되고 있는지 알고 싶어서
I need to know everything's
going all right.
여자애는 여전히 살아있어?
Is she still alive?
걱정마, 파리드
Don't worry, Farid.
그 애가 말을 해야하니까
We need her to talk.
그 애가 말을 할 필요가 없어질때는,
모든게 끝났을꺼야
And when we don't need her
to talk, we'll be done.
저 통화로 뭘 하려는겁니까?
What good did that do?
저 통화는 세상에서 최고의 장비로
That call's gonna be analyzed
분석이 되어질겁니다
by some of the best equipment on earth.
당신 도움이 필요해요
I do need your help.
[Camera whirring]
만약 내가 감시를 하지 않고 있었다면요?
Cassandra: And if I
hadn't been listening in?
- 그런일이 일어난적 있었어요?
- 사실 없지요
- When does that happen?
- Never, actually.
추적하기에는 통화가 너무 짧았지만
Call was too short to trace,
통신 회사를 이용해서 정보를 뽑아냈지요
but I pulled a little trick
with the signal agency.
그들은 여전히 라스베가스
기지국 범위내에 있어요
They're still inside the
Vegas cell tower array.
그들은 도시 안에 있어요
They're here in the city.
교통 카메라들이 도주용 자동차인
Traffic cameras tagged a black van
검정색 밴을 포착했네요
as the getaway vehicle.
여러명의 부하들과, 검정색 밴
그리고 소녀를 감금해두려면
Big crew, black van, plus
holding for the girl.
저들은 작전 기지가 필요하겠군요
They're gonna need a base of operations.
친구와 대화를 해봐야겠네요
I'm gonna chat with a friend.
당신은 역사상 가장 큰
You have access to the greatest
정보 데이터베이스에 접속할 수 있는데
intelligence database in world history,
친구를 만난다구요?
and you have a friend?
기술에 의존하지 않는것이 최고의 기술이죠
Low-tech's the best tech.
も
[Indistinct conversations]
널 믿는다, 빅터
기억해, 검정색 밴이야
I'm counting on you, Victor.
Remember, it's a black van.
알았지? 이거 받아둬
Yeah? Here.
[Ring tone playing]
여보세요?
- [Cellphone beeps]
- Hello?
알렉스 케인이요? 전화 잘못 걸었어요
Alex Kane? You have the wrong number.
- 실례합니다, 미안해요
- 이봐요!
- Excuse me. I'm sorry.
- Hey!
비밀에 관한 규칙이 뭐였죠?
What was that rule about secrecy?
당신 핸드폰 배터리가
다됐다구요, 멍청하긴
Your cell battery's dead, you idiot.
이걸 보여줘야 해서요
I need to show you this.
길 건너를 보세요
Across the street.
네, 공식적으로 당신이 할 수 있는
일에 소름이 끼치네요
Yeah, I'm officially
terrified of what you can do.
그들은 오후 4시까지
송금을 하라고 했어요
They say wire the money by 4:00 P.M.
[ Sniffles]
그들은 아빠 엄마에게 이 번호가
필요할거라고 했어요
They say all you need is this number.
[ Sniffles, whimpers]
놈들은 마지막 순간에 요구될
생존 증거에 대비해서
They're gonna keep Shada alive
계속 샤다를 살려둘꺼에요
in case of a last-minute proof of life.
그리고 송금이 완전히 들어오게 되면
저 아이를 죽일거에요
And then they're gonna kill
her as soon as the funds clear.
[Sighs]
내가 뭘 해야 하지?
What do I do?
제발 지니, 나를 도와줘
Come on, Ginny. Help me out here.
내가 뭘 해야 하지?
What do I do?
좋은 일을 해야죠
You do good.
비디오는 기지를 압축해내는데
충분한 데이터이지만
Video is enough data to narrow it down,
정확하지는 않아요
but not exact.
도시 북동쪽 외곽의
95번 도로 지역이에요
Northeast corner of the
city in the Route 95 pocket.
왜 홈리스 구호소에 간거죠?
Why are you at a homeless shelter?
이 도시에는 납치범들이 기지로 사용할만한
There's only so many places in this city
너무 많은 장소들이 있어요
that kidnappers can use as a base.
수색하기에는 너무 많지요
Still too many to search.
라스베가스에는 10,000명의
부랑자들이 있어요
10,000 homeless in Vegas.
[Horn blares]
도시 안에 버려진 건물이 있다면
If there's an abandoned
building in this city,
누군가는 그곳에서 자고 있지요
somebody's sleeping in it.
그리고 만약 그 건물이 갑자기
총을 든 사람들로 가득 채워지면
And if that building was
suddenly filled by men with guns,
부랑자들은 서로 경고를 해줘요
they'd warn each other.
제법인대요
Look at you, low-tech.
알렉스! 알아냈어요
Alex! Got a place.
고속도로 옆의 비어있던 상가 건물이요
Empty mall out by the highway.
디에고가 지난주에
총을 든 사람들한테 쫓겨났대요
Diego got cleared out last week
by some guys with some guns.
그들 말로는 보안팀이라고 했다는데
제복을 입지는 않았었대요
Said they were security,
but with no uniforms.
그리고 검정색 밴이 있었구요
And there was a black van.
- 95번 도로 북쪽이야?
- 네
- North of the 95?
- Yeah.
안내해줘
Show me.
[Computer whirring]
[Keyboard clacking]
송금은 아직인가?
Wire transfer done yet?
곧 완료됩니다
Any second now.
[Computer beeps]
[Sniffles]
[Dirt bike motor revving]
Yeah, you come taggin' along
exhibit "a" on the
tray, what you say?
As I throw it in your face
exhibit "b," what you see?
Well, that's me
I put it back in your place
yeah, I done it before
and I can do it some more
so what you waiting for?
Yeah, I was right all along
'cause I have done it before
and I can do it some more
I got my eye on the score
I'm gonna cut to the core
it's too late, it's
too soon, or is it?
Tick, tick, tick, tick
tick, tick, boom
check it
も
Aah!
알렉스!
- Alex!
- [Bullet ricochets]
- 이 아이를 죽일꺼야!
- 알렉스!
- I'm gonna kill her!
- Alex!
케인!
Kane!
나와 소녀중에 선택해, 케인
둘다 가질수는 없을껄
Me or the girl, Kane. Can't have us both.
It's too late, too late, too late
too la-a-a-a-a-Te
oh, ye-e-e-e-e-ah
- 뭘 해야하죠?
- 빠져나가야지
- What are we doing?
- We have to get out.
단단히 붙어 있어. 놈들이 너무 많아
Hold tight. There's too many.
무기를 버려! 꼼짝마!
- [Sirens wailing]
- Drop your weapons! Freeze!
- 무기를 버려!
- Drop your weapons!
- Drop them!
- 손 들어!
- 무기를 버려!
- Let me see your hands!
- Throw it down!
알았어요, 알았어
It's okay. It's okay.
알렉스
Alex.
엎드려! 꼼짝마
Man: Sit down! Stay there.
괜찮아
Brown: All right.
[Indistinct shouting]
- 알렉스, 알렉...
- 샤다, 괜찮을꺼야
- Alex. Ale...
- Shada, you're gonna be all right.
괜찮을꺼야
You're gonna be fine.
좋아, 손을 보이는곳에 놔
All right, hands where I can see them.
[Shouting continues]
[Handcuffs click]
Tick, tick, tick, tick
tick, tick, boom
자네한테 행운스럽게도,
비포장 도로 오토바이 타는 아이들이
Well, lucky for you, those
dirt-bike kids called 911
총소리를 듣고 911로 전화를 했다구?
when they heard gunshots, huh?
행운이지
Lucky.
납치범들이 공격할거라는걸
어떻게 알게 된거야?
How did you know the kidnappers
were gonna hit the Charlemagne?
답을 안하는군
No answer.
자네 FBI 파일을 받았어
Brown: Pulled your FBI file.
자네가 이 자들 전부를 죽였어?
You killed all these guys?
수단, 터키, 요르단, 우크라이나
Sudan, Turkey, Jordan, Ukraine.
도대체 뭔 짓을 한거야, 친구?
What the hell, man?
FBI가 자네를 특수임무에 파견한건
FBI put you on a task force
테러리스트들을 찾으라고 보낸거지
그들을 죽이라고 보낸게 아니었어
to find terrorists, not kill them.
이건 적법한 절차가 아니야
This is not due process.
자네 깜짝 놀랐겠군
You'd be surprised.
반격하는 것에서 선제 공격하는것으로
바뀌는데는 아주 작은 차이밖에 없어
It's a small step to go from
shooting back to shooting first.
틀렸어
Well, it's wrong.
절대 틀린거지
Absolutely wrong.
그리고 나는 그걸 좋아했고
And I liked it.
스스로에게 생명을 구하고 있다고 말했어
I tell myself I'm saving lives,
하지만 세네명을 잡아넣은후
더 이상 올바른 이유로
but three or four guys in,
I can't even pretend anymore
일을 하고 있는 척 할 수가 없었어
I'm doing it for the right reasons.
하지만 그들을 사냥하는건 잘했지
But I'm good at hunting them.
그래서 수단에서 총을 맞을 때까지
계속 사냥을 했지
So I keep going till I
take a bullet in the Sudan.
그리고 웃긴게...지니라는 이름의
기막힌 의사가 내 상처를 봉합해줬지
And this funny... Quirky
doctor named Ginny sews me up.
샤다
- [Door opens]
- Daoud: Shada.
[Gasps]
[Exhales sharply]
날 감옥에 넣길 원해?
You want to throw me in prison?
좋아
Okay.
지니는 죽었어
Ginny's gone.
만약 내가 여길 나가면...
If I'm out here...
다시 이 남자로 돌아가고 싶지 않아
I don't want to be this guy again.
[Papers thud]
형사님, 케인씨 일로
FBI 요원이 왔습니다
Detective, there's an FBI
agent here about Mr. Kane.
이 자를 감시할까요?
Do you want me to watch him?
글쎄, 지난번에 그게 잘 통했었나?
Well, that worked out great last time.
우리와 함께 데려가자구
Take him with us.
알겠습니다
Yes, sir.
여기, 총잡이가 멈춰서 돌아서고
Johnson: Here, you can
see the gunman stop, turn,
케인씨에게 총을 쏘는게 보이죠
and fire at Mr. Kane.
그리고 여기, 차가 케인씨를
치는걸 볼 수 있을겁니다
And here, you can see the car hit Mr. Kane.
Ooh. Ouch.
그리고 여기, 총잡이가 검정색 밴으로
And here, you can see
도망치는걸 볼수 있을겁니다
where the gunman escapes in the black van.
저자가 당신들의 납치 사건에
연관되었다고 생각합니다
I believe that's tied
to your kidnapping case.
이 영상을 어디서 확보한겁니까?
Where did you get this footage?
FBI는 여러 주에 걸쳐있는
자동차 도난 조직을 조사중인데
Well, the FBI's investigating
an interstate car-theft ring,
어거스틴 카지노 주차장의 보안카메라에서
and we just got this off
of the security cameras
이것을 확보했습니다
of the Augustine Casino parking lot.
어제 이걸 봤으면 좋았을텐데요
Would have been nice to see this yesterday.
그게, 오늘 아침 검토할때까지
Well, we had no idea
이 영상에 무엇이 있었는지
알지 못했습니다
that this was on the tape until
we reviewed it in the morning.
제가 장담하건대
Look, I assure you
라스베가스 경찰과 케인씨에게
both the Las Vegas Police Department
FBI가 심심한 사과를 드리는 바입니다
and Mr. Kane have the
Bureaus full apology.
이 비디오 증거가
I believe that this video evidence
그를 석방할 수 있다고 믿습니다
actually exonerates him.
이건 시작일뿐입니다
This is a start.
저희는 전방위적인 조사중입니다
We still have a full investigation.
그리고 케인씨는 지금...
And Mr. Kane is now way...
제가 확실하게 말씀을 안드린것 같군요
Maybe I was unclear.
주 정부와 검찰은 이미 이 사건의
You see, the, uh, state
and the district attorney
모든 증거를 검토했습니다
have already reviewed all
of the evidence in this case
그리고 케인씨에게 아무런 혐의도
없다는데 동의했습니다
and, uh, have agreed that Mr.
Kane is to face no charges.
그는 방면이 됐습니다
He's free to go.
[Chuckles]
그게, 저는 여전히 납치에 관하여
물어볼 질문들이 있습니다
Well, I still need him to answer
questions about the kidnapping.
FBI가 사건을 맡을겁니다
The Bureau's gonna take
that off your plate.
우리의 관할사건이거든요
Being that it is our jurisdiction and all.
가능한 빨리 모든 증거와 기록들을
You can send over all of
the evidence and recordings
보내주시기 바랍니다
as soon as possible.
젊은이, 자네 아주 지독한 하루를 보냈군
[Chuckles] Son, you done
had one hell of a day.
아주 지독했겠군
I feel awful about this.
집에 데려다 주겠네
Let me offer you a ride home.
괜찮아요
I'm fine.
데려다줄께
I insist.
자네가 가야할 곳에 정확히 데려다 주겠네
I'm gonna take you exactly
where you need to go.
[Clears throat]
[Sighs]
[Handcuffs click]
믿든 안믿든간에
Alex: For what it's worth,
자네는 내가 알고 있는 최고의 경찰이야
you're the best cop I've ever known.
무슨 일에 연루된거야, 알렉스?
What the hell are you into, Alex?
여러분, 좋은 하루 되시오
Uh, you boys have a nice day.
も
우리가 그 테입을 먼저 찾지
못했다는걸 믿을 수 없군요
I can't believe we didn't
find that tape first.
자네가 걱정할 문제가 아니야
Don't worry yourself about it.
그 영상에 대한 영장을
받을 수도 없었을거야
We never would have gotten
a warrant for that footage.
연방 사건이라서요?
Because it's a federal case?
그 카지노의 주차장에는
Because there aren't any security cameras
보안카메라가 없거든
in the parking lot of that casino.
も
[Car doors close]
여기가 날 쏴버릴 장소인가요?
This where you shoot me?
당신을 쏴요?
알렉스, 당신은 총상을 입었어요
Shoot you? Alex, you're a hit.
당신에게 일을 제안하는거에요
We're offering you a job.
제가 일전에 당신에게 제대로
말씀을 못드린것 같군요, 케인씨
I'm afraid I misled you earlier, Mr. Kane,
하우스에는 늘 두명이
있다고 말했을때 말이에요
when I said that there were
always two members of the house.
사실 세명으로 구성이됩니다
There are always three.
그 도박사들은...베팅을 할
누군가가 필요해요
See, the gamblers... They
need someone to bet on.
그래서 우리는 플레이어를 만들죠
So we created the player.
한 사람에게...최악의 인간성에 대항할
One man... one man and his
resources and ingenuity
자산과 정교한 지원이 제안하는 바입니다
set against the worst
humanity has to offer.
그럼 그들이 나에게 베팅을 하나요?
So they would bet on me?
몇몇은 당신의 반대쪽에 베팅을 하지요
Mm, some would bet against you.
기분나쁘게 받아드리지는 마세요
Don't take it personally.
그럼, 케인씨, 우리의 플레이어가
되어 주시겠습니까?
So, Mr. Kane, will you be our player?
[Laughs]
당신들이 가진 모든것으로...
당신들은 엄청난 고통을 막을 수 있었어요
All you have... You
could stop so much pain,
하지만 그 대신에, 당신들은
당신들의 즐거움을 위하여 사람들의 목숨에
but instead, you gamble with people's lives
도박을 했어요
for your amusement.
[Chuckles]
저기 뭐가 보입니까, 케인씨?
What do you see out there, Mr. Kane?
도시요
A city.
나는 배출구가 보입니다
I see a safety valve.
사람들은 그들의 기본족인 욕망을 위한
배출구를 필요로 하죠
People need an outlet
for their base desires
그렇지 않다면 사람들은 행동을 합니다
or else they will act out.
도박사들도 다를바가 없습니다
The gamblers are no different,
그들이 행동을 할때는
except that when they act out,
국가를 파괴하고 지도를 새로
그린다는것을 제외하고는요
they destroy nations, rewrite maps.
대통령들을 죽이구요
Kill presidents.
싫습니다
No.
싫습니까?
No?
뭐, 이게 다입니까?
What, that's it?
가서 다른 사람을 찾는거에요?
You just go find some other guy?
항상 게임이 존재했어요, 케인씨
There's always a game, Mr. Kane.
항상 하우스가 존재했구요
There is always the house.
항상 핏 보스와 딜러가 있었죠
There is always the pit
boss and the dealer.
그리고 항상...항상,
무슨 일이 있든간에...
And there is always...
Always, no matter what...
또다른 플레이어가 있었죠
Another player.
하지만 또다른 플레이어는
결코 납치된 소녀를 구하기 위해
But another player who'd
never risk his life
스스로 목숨을 걸지는 않겠죠
to save a kidnapped girl.
당신은 게임에 말려든
선량한 사람들에게 일어난 일을
You're the first player who
cared about what happened
걱정하는 첫번째 플레이어 입니다
to the innocents caught in the game,
실제로 사람들을 돕길 원하는 플레이어요
a player who actually
wanted to help people.
당신이 어떤 선을
행할 수 있을지 생각해보세요
Imagine what good you could do.
마지막 플레이어에게 무슨일이 일어난거죠?
What happened to the last player?
[Scoffs lightly]
[Car door opens, closes]
[Engine turns over]
알렉스, 내가 이렇게
해줄 수 없는걸 알잖나
Man: Alex, you know I
shouldn't be doing this.
이건 그녀의 것이야, 내것이 아니고
This is hers, not mine.
자네에게 시간을 좀 주겠네
I'll, um, let you have a moment.
그냥 문신이잖아
It's just a tattoo.
누가 그녀를 이송해왔지?
[Clears throat, sniffles] Who brought her in?
어떤 FBI 요원이 서류에 싸인을 했는데
Some FBI agent signed off on the paperwork.
も
[Elevator bell dings]
그가 당신을 창문 밖으로
던져버리려고 왔어요
He's here to throw you out the window.
당신들의 플레이어가 되겠어요
I'm your player.
규칙들을 이해하죠
You understand the rules.
카산드라를 제외하고는 누구에게도
도움을 요청할 수 없습니다
You can never ask for help
from anyone except Cassandra.
게임의 존재를 밝힐수도 없습니다
You can never reveal the
existence of the game.
그리고 종신 계약입니다
And it's a lifetime appointment.
하우스에 합류한걸 환영합니다
Welcome to the house.
오, 그리고 케인씨,
절 실망시키지 마세요
Oh, and, Mr. Kane, don't disappoint me.
내가 호출하면, 당신은 와야해요
If I call, you come.
그건 베팅이 시작된거라는 의미거든요
It means a bet is in play.
우리는 당신을 다시 볼거라고
생각하지 못했어요
We didn't think we'd see you again.
그래요, 나는 혼자 잘 할 수 없거든요
Yeah, I don't do well on my own.
빈 손이니까요
Idle hands.
게다가, 당신들은 세상에서
최고의 데이터를 보유하고 있지요
Besides, you have the
best data in the world.
어쩌면 지니의 죽음에 책임있는
사람을 찾을수도 있겠죠
Maybe I can find the person
responsible for Ginny.
그리고 나서는요?
And then?
그들은 후회할거에요
They'll be sorry.
그들이 누구이든지간에, 후회할거에요
Whoever they are, they'll be sorry.
좋아요
Fair enough.
も
[Elevator bell dings]
[Computer whirring]
[Computer beeps]
베팅을 해보세요
Place your bets.
[Computer beeps]
も
[Snaps fingers]
Synced and corrected by martythecrazy
www.addic7ed.com
Kor sub: bravesfan
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.addic7ed.com -